lafalafa.com 2018-03-14

# Coupons, Discounts and Extra Cashback savings – LafaLafa.com – Join Free

We understand the value of your privacy and make the utmost effort to ensure that your personal information always stays secure. Our privacy policy here will attempt to explain to you what information we collect about you, how we collect it, why we collect it, how this information is used, how it is shared with any other third parties and the choices you have concerning its use. 

##### LafaLafa .com ("website", "our website", "site","Mobile App") is operated by Yellow Brick Road Digital Marketing Pvt. Ltd. ("We", "Our", "Company").

#### What information do we collect about you or from you and store in our system

## Your Personal information

When you signup for the Lafalafa service, we collect your name and email address (either via email and password registration or via Google+ or Facebook registration. For Facebook and Google+ registration we may also get some additional information as given by these platforms). Your IP address is also captured by us for security purposes. If you have downloaded the Mobile app then we also capture your device information for security purposes (e.g. your device ID, your registered email address for google Play, push token, location etc).On our mobile app we also collect and verify your mobile number using a one time password which is sent to you via SMS, and in order to seamlessly enter the OTP in your mobile app, the app checks your SMS inbox for when this particular SMS is received and the OTP in the SMS. The app would not be reading any other SMS or storing information from any other SMS except for searching for the OTP sent by the app. Your email address is critical for seamless communication between you and LafaLafa as we send all information related to your transactions and cashback to your email address (registration confirmation, forgot password, cashback tracked, cashback approved etc). If you only subscribe for LafaLafa newsletter, we collect your email address and will email our promotional newsletter with all the latest offers to you. You may at any time unsubscribe from our newsletter if you find the offers are not relevant for you. We may also from time to time use your mobile number to send relevant offers via SMS to you.

One mobile number can only be registered with one email address and you maybe able to update your mobile number using the settings section on the LafaLafa website which will enable us to serve your queries better and give you our high level of customer support. Your mobile number will also be needed in the redemption section if you wish to receive mobile recharge as a redemption option.

We may request and collect more personal information from you at specific occasions or on the website/mobile application so that we understand your profile better and can give you more relevant offers as per your profile and preferences e.g. when you last opened the app or the other shopping mobile apps you use or when you last logged into the website.

We are against spamming of our customers and if you would like to report an incident of spamming, please contact us so we can investigate and take appropriate action.

## Your Bank Account or Redemption information

We will also collect your Bank Account information (Bank Name, Bank Account number, IFSC Code, Bank Branch) in order to be able to process cashback payments to your bank account by bank transfer. Other methods of payment like mobile recharge also need appropriate information like your mobile number and telecom provider and Shopping Vouchers would be digitally emailed to you.

## Your usage details for the Website/ Mobile App

We keep a track of your usage of our website like when you logged in, where you logged in from, your IP address from the website/Your location from the mobile app which enables us to make the user experience on the website better for you. We also track every click from our website/mobile app to any store via you as this is essential for us to track your transactions and attribute the cashback due to you. While we display bank offers but we do not collect or store any of your credit card information. In the event that we need to use your information for any purpose not explicitly stated in our terms and conditions, privacy policy or on the Website, the we will explicitly seek your permission to do so.

## Sharing information and use of third parties

We do not share any of your personal details with any third party unless you may specifically give us your consent to do so. However, we may share your details with stores/retailers/store's affiliate networks in order to track and confirm your transactions at these stores and validate your cashback earnings and specially when you place a missing cashback request. We may also need to share your information with other organizations that assist us in our various processes for transaction tracking, fraud detection and advertising amongst other processes. We may use third parties to host, operate various features made available, send emails, analyze data, mobile app attribution tracking, push notifications etc. Some of these third parties may need access to your personal information in order to make the services provided through our website or mobile application work. 

We may also be bound to share your information if we are forced to do so by the law, or receive a valid request by a law enforcement or government authority.

In the event of a merger, acquisition or sale of LafaLafa.com, you would be duly notified about the change of ownership status or use of your personal information.

In order to advertise our service, we tie up with and contract with multiple third parties to serve advertisements (banners, SEO, SEM, Facebook Ad's, Twitter Ad's amongst others) on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this Website as well. Such third parties may also collect information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services and subsequently may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This information is collected through the use of a pixel tag (Google uses cookies called DART), which is industry standard technology used by most major websites and platforms. Such third parties are not permitted to sell or share your personally identifiable information as part of this process. Sometimes users may opt out of the use of such tracking e.g. For Google you may disable tracking by DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

## The use of Cookies and Cookie Policy

A cookie is a small piece of information/data which is transferred from a website to the cookie file of the browser (like Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer etc) on your computer's hard drive. The browser enables to save this information and sends it back to the website server whenever the website is opened on the browser.

The usual information that a cookie will contain is the name of the domain (internet location) from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie (i.e. when does it expire), and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. 

Such cookies help to provide us details such as the retailer/store on which you have shopped on, the exact timing of the purchase and other relevant details. Cookies also help us to keep a record of your preferences, so we can present you offers and promotions best suited to your needs, interest & previous transaction behaviour and are used by many major websites as an industry standard. 

##### The types of cookies used on this website/mobile browser are :

  * Session cookies which are temporary and remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site.
  * Persistent cookies which remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie as per the configulation set for it).

**Please note :** if you disable the cookies in your browser which are used to track your purchases via our website, you will not be able to earn cashback / points when you shop via our website. Please also note that a number of stores/store's affiliate networks have not enabled cookie tracking on their mobile websites and thus cashback tracking may not work effectively on mobile browsers. 

## Security

It is our prime concern to keep your personal information secure and we employ the best fit-for-purpose security measures for the same. Your information is stored on secure servers with restricted access. However, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your information as complete security of information during transmission is virtually impossible and thus the security during such times is deemed as fit-for-purpose. You may at any time contact us for any concerns related to our security measures. 

## Updating Your Personal information and settings

We understand that customers get a number of promotional mailers which maybe a nuisance for you, thus we always enable the option to unsubscribe from our promotional newsletter mailers. However, as we require to send you periodic updates about your account as well as about your cashback tracking, hence unsubscribing from such system/transactional mailers is not optional. Your bank account information, mobile number etc can be modified at any time however your email address and name are your unique identifiers for this service and cannot be modified. 

For any queries related to our service, please feel free to contact us at **wecare@lafalafa.com** .
